http://www.icmi.com.au/privacypolicy

TALK TO A CONSULTANT ABOUT YOUR EVENT
1800 334 625 or Send a message
View Shortlist
Close menu
Speaker CategoriesSpeakersAfter Dinner SpeakersBusinessCEO's & Entrepreneur SpeakersCustomer Service SpeakersHuman Resources SpeakersMedia SpeakersRetail SpeakersSales and Marketing SpeakersTime Management SpeakersChange Management SpeakersWomen in Business SpeakersAdvertising & Marketing SpeakersBusiness SpeakersTeamwork SpeakersCelebrity SpeakersCelebrity SpeakersFood, Wine & EtiquetteChef SpeakersCelebrity ChefFood, Wine & Etiquette SpeakersHealth, Lifestyle & Wellbeing speakersOH&S SpeakersMindfulness SpeakersMental Illness & HealthHealth, Lifestyle and Wellbeing SpeakersLeadershipLeadership SpeakersWomen in LeadershipMaster of Ceremonies, Hosts & FacilitatorsFacilitatorsMaster of Ceremonies (Entertaining)Master of Ceremonies (MC's)SportsOlympic SpeakersSports SpeakersMotivational & InspirationalAdventurerInspirational SpeakersMotivational SpeakersEducationLaw & PoliticsPolitical SpeakersLaw & Crime SpeakersSocial Trends & Current AffairsCurrent Affairs SpeakersDiversity & Inclusion SpeakersEnvironment, Climate Change SpeakersGeneration X & Y SpeakersWorld Affairs SpeakersSocial Trends & Issues SpeakersTechnology, Future & InnovationCreativity and Innovation SpeakersDigital DisruptionFuturistsSocial Media & Networking SpeakersTEDxVirtual PresenterEconomy & FinanceEconomics and Finance SpeakersTeam BuildingFun & Themed ActivitiesCommunications Activities for TeamsIndoor Activities for TeamsLeadership Team ActivitiesTeam WorkNegotiation Activities for TeamsOutdoor Team ActivitiesTeam ChangeEntertainmentBands & MusiciansComediansAfter Dinner EntertainmentCabaret & Variety ArtistsCelebrity ComediansCelebrity Singers and ArtistsCircus ActsCorporate HumorHoaxImpersonatorMagicianRoving EntertainmentTravelling SpeakersInternational SpeakersNew Zealand SpeakersEnquire NowBlogFAQAboutOur PeopleContact Us
Speaker CategoriesSpeakersAfter Dinner SpeakersBusinessCEO's & Entrepreneur SpeakersCustomer Service SpeakersHuman Resources SpeakersMedia SpeakersRetail SpeakersSales and Marketing SpeakersTime Management SpeakersChange Management SpeakersWomen in Business SpeakersAdvertising & Marketing SpeakersBusiness SpeakersTeamwork SpeakersCelebrity SpeakersCelebrity SpeakersFood, Wine & EtiquetteChef SpeakersCelebrity ChefFood, Wine & Etiquette SpeakersHealth, Lifestyle & Wellbeing speakersOH&S SpeakersMindfulness SpeakersMental Illness & HealthHealth, Lifestyle and Wellbeing SpeakersLeadershipLeadership SpeakersWomen in LeadershipMaster of Ceremonies, Hosts & FacilitatorsFacilitatorsMaster of Ceremonies (Entertaining)Master of Ceremonies (MC's)SportsOlympic SpeakersSports SpeakersMotivational & InspirationalAdventurerInspirational SpeakersMotivational SpeakersEducationLaw & PoliticsPolitical SpeakersLaw & Crime SpeakersSocial Trends & Current AffairsCurrent Affairs SpeakersDiversity & Inclusion SpeakersEnvironment, Climate Change SpeakersGeneration X & Y SpeakersWorld Affairs SpeakersSocial Trends & Issues SpeakersTechnology, Future & InnovationCreativity and Innovation SpeakersDigital DisruptionFuturistsSocial Media & Networking SpeakersTEDxVirtual PresenterEconomy & FinanceEconomics and Finance SpeakersTeam BuildingFun & Themed ActivitiesCommunications Activities for TeamsIndoor Activities for TeamsLeadership Team ActivitiesTeam WorkNegotiation Activities for TeamsOutdoor Team ActivitiesTeam ChangeEntertainmentBands & MusiciansComediansAfter Dinner EntertainmentCabaret & Variety ArtistsCelebrity ComediansCelebrity Singers and ArtistsCircus ActsCorporate HumorHoaxImpersonatorMagicianRoving EntertainmentTravelling SpeakersInternational SpeakersNew Zealand SpeakersEnquire NowBlogFAQAboutOur PeopleContact Us
Welcome to ICMI’s Privacy Policy.
At ICMI, we recognise the importance of your privacy and understand your concerns about the security of the personal information you provide to us.  We comply with the Australian Privacy Principles (APPs) as contained in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth).  The APPs detail how personal information may be collected, used, disclosed, stored and destroyed, and how an individual may gain access to or make complaints about the personal information held about them.
“Personal information” is information or an opinion about an identified individual, or about an individual who is reasonably identifiable.
“Sensitive information”, a sub-set of personal information, is information or an opinion about an individual’s racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, political association membership, religious beliefs or affiliations, philosophical beliefs, professional or trade association membership, trade union membership, sexual orientation or practices or criminal record, and includes health information and genetic information.
This Privacy Policy details how ICMI manages personal information about you.
What personal information we collect and hold
The kinds of personal information we collect from you or about you depend on the transaction you have entered into with us, the services you or your organisation have contracted us to provide, and the services you or your organisation are interested in.
The kinds of personal information that we commonly collect and hold from you or about you include:  your name, address, phone and fax numbers, email address, date of birth, driver licence details, passport details, travel preferences, bank account details, credit card details and information about your preferences for speakers / our consulting services. However, the personal information that we actually collect from you will vary depending on whether you are a client or a speaker.
How we collect and hold personal information
We aim to collect personal information only directly from you, unless it is unreasonable or impracticable for us to do so.  For example, we may collect personal information from you or about you from letters, emails, enquiries, application forms and contracts that you submit to us, telephone calls with us, your activity on our website and from your attendance and participation at the events and functions that we hold.
In some instances, we may receive personal information about you from third parties, including our business affiliates.
You can be anonymous or use a pseudonym when dealing with us, unless:
- the use of your true identity is a legal requirement; or
- it is impracticable for us to deal with you on such basis.
If we do not collect or hold your personal information, or if you do not provide your consent for us to do so, then we may not be able to answer your enquiry, complete the transaction you have entered into, or provide the services that you or your organisation have contracted us to provide.
Generally, we do not collect sensitive information. We may collect sensitive information from you or about you where there is a legal requirement to do so, or where we are otherwise permitted by law.  In all other situations, we will specifically seek your consent prior to collecting such information.
Why we collect, hold, use and disclose personal information
We collect, hold, use and disclose personal information from you or about you where it is reasonably necessary for us to carry out our business functions and activities.  For example, we collect, hold, use and disclose your personal information as necessary to provide our consulting services to you or your organisation, and to arrange speakers / entertainers for your events.
We also collect, hold, use and disclose your personal information for related purposes that you would reasonably expect, such as our administrative and accounting functions, fraud checks, providing you with information about other services offered by us, marketing and promotions, market research, newsletter communications, statistical collation and website traffic analysis.
Our business works closely with entities associated with our business, including our franchisee, consultant, and speaker / entertainer networks. We routinely disclose your personal information to these third parties to enable them to assist us in carrying out our business functions and activities.  We will also disclose your personal information to banking institutions in order to verify and process your payments.
With respect to any of events connected to us or our services, if you buy a ticket a record of your booking data may be made available to our partners (e.g the client, event organiser or venue) for their records, analysis and to allow them to operate their event effectively.
At the time when you provide your personal information, you may also ‘opt in’ to receive future communications from our event partners, including event organisers, venues and sponsors and they may contact you with marketing messages relating to upcoming events, offers, newsletters and other promotional material. If you no longer wish to receive such communications from our partners, you will need to contact them to unsubscribe from their lists.
We may disclose your personal information in the following circumstances:
- If we sell or buy any business assets (or the business itself) and are required to disclose personal information to prospective buyers or sellers;
- If we are required by law to disclose such information; and
- If we need to use such information to enforce any of our agreements, or to protect the rights, property or safety of ourselves or others.
We may use and disclose non-personally identifiable information in aggregate form to improve the Site and our services and to assist our advertising partners with targeted advertising.
Opting out
When we send you an email, we will clearly state who the email is from and provide clear information on how to contact us. In addition, all marketing emails from us will contain instructions on how to remove yourself from our mailing list.
Cookies
Our website may use ‘cookies’ which is when a website transfers certain data to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. They allow us to track usage patterns and to compile data that can help us improve our content and target advertising. You can change your cookie settings in your browser.
Links to third party sites
We are not responsible for the content or practices of websites operated by third parties that are linked to our website. These links are meant for your convenience only and you agree that once you leave our website via such a link, you are responsible for checking the applicable privacy policy of the third-party site.
How we hold and store personal information
Your personal information is held and stored on paper, by electronic means or both.  We have physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in place for personal information and take reasonable steps to ensure that your personal information is protected from misuse, interference, loss and unauthorised access, modification and disclosure. Our staff members receive regular training on privacy procedures.  Unfortunately, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be totally secure and we will not be liable in the event of third party hacking or other security breach outside our reasonable control.
Destruction and de-identification
We will retain your personal information whilst it is required for any of our business functions, or for any other lawful purpose.
We use secure methods to destroy or to permanently de-identify your personal information when it is no longer needed.
Overseas disclosure
Our business is affiliated with other businesses, organisations and people located overseas. In the course of doing business with you, we may disclose some of your personal information to overseas recipients located in New Zealand, Indonesia, Hong Kong, Fiji, the United States of America and the United Kingdom.
However, in any event, we will not disclose your personal information to an overseas recipient unless:
- it is necessary to complete the transaction you have entered into, including retaining such historical information for our future consulting services; and
- you have provided consent; or
- we believe on reasonable grounds that the overseas recipient is required to deal with your personal information by enforceable laws which are similar to the requirements under the APPs; or
it is otherwise permitted by law.
Requests for access and correction
We have procedures in place for dealing with and responding to requests for access to, and correction of, the personal information held about you.
In most cases, we expect that we will be able to comply with your request.  However, if we do not agree to provide you access or to correct the information as requested, we will give you written reasons for our decision.  For further information, please contact us.
To assist us to keep our records up-to-date, please notify us of any changes to your personal information.
Complaints and concerns
We have procedures in place for dealing with complaints and concerns about our practices in relation to the Privacy Act and the APPs.  We will respond to your complaint in accordance with the relevant provisions of the APPs.  For further information, please contact us.
Contact
Privacy Officer
Inform Communicate Motivate International (Australia) Pty Ltd
I'm looking for:
Body Language, Voice and Confident Leadership“The amateur practises until they get it ....
Read More
Maggie Beer AM
An essential ingredient in any discussion about food and flavour, Maggie Beer AM is ....
Read More
Mark Carter
Creating a culture that embraces change, peak performance and adaptability
With ....
Read More
Sir Bob Geldof
As a campaigner for numerous causes throughout the world, Sir Bob Geldof is ....
Read More
Christine Nixon APM
Women in leadership, succeeding in complex circumstances
Christine Nixon shares with her audiences ....
Read More
Privacy © 2016 Copyright ICMI. All Rights Reserved.
Website by Beautiful Websites
